[
    {
        "questionNo": "Q1",
        "question": "Saanvi and Mateo found 8 chocolate bars. They bought 5. How many were left?",
        "options": [
            "3",
            "4",
            "2",
            "5"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q2",
        "question": "They saw 12 apple juices on the shelf. They chose 7. How many were still there?",
        "options": [
            "6",
            "5",
            "4",
            "7"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q3",
        "question": "Saanvi got 8 lollipops. Mateo got 6 more lollipops. How many apples do they have in total?",
        "options": [
            "15",
            "14",
            "16",
            "13"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q4",
        "question": "Saanvi found 6 cookies. Mateo found 5 more cookies. How many cookies do they have together?",
        "options": [
            "10",
            "9",
            "11",
            "8"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q5",
        "question": "They found 15 packets of chips. They bought 10. How many were left?",
        "options": [
            "4",
            "3",
            "5",
            "6"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q6",
        "question": "Mateo had 19 marbles but he lost 6 marbles. How many marbles does Mateo have now?",
        "options": [
            "11",
            "14",
            "12",
            "13"
        ],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q7",
        "question": "Saanvi found 16 bags of popcorn. If she gave 12 to Mateo, how many does she have left?",
        "options": [
            "5",
            "4",
            "3",
            "2"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q8",
        "question": "Mateo bought 15 bottles of apple juice. Saanvi added 12 more bottles. How many bottles of apple juice do they have now?",
        "options": [
            "27",
            "26",
            "24",
            "25"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q9",
        "question": "Saanvi bought 15 muffins. Mateo bought 13 more muffins. How many muffins do they have in total?",
        "options": [
            "27",
            "29",
            "28",
            "30"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q10",
        "question": "They found 25 packets of candies on a shelf. They bought 10. How many were left on the shelf?",
        "options": [
            "14",
            "15",
            "13",
            "16"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    }
]
